https://ibookholiday.com/services/privacy

Login
Forgot Your Password?
Enter your email address and we'll send you a link to reset your password
Privacy Policy
At I book Holiday we are committed in earning the trust of our clients by adopting high standards in the protection and management of personal information. Our policy outlines the kind of personal information we collect and receive, the circumstances in which we collect or receive personal information and the policies for sharing certain types of personal information in certain limited circumstances. In this policy 'I Book Holiday DMCC' means I Book Holiday a Dubai Multi Commodities Centre (DMCC) incorporated in Dubai, United Arab Emirates. The term "you" refers to the “customer” associated client visiting the website and / or booking a reservation through us on this website, or through our customer service agents. By visiting the www.ibookholiday.com website (the "website"), you are accepting the practices described herein.
Our policy outlines the kind of personal information we collect and receive, the circumstances in which we collect or receive personal information, and the policies for sharing certain types of personal information in certain limited circumstances.
The methods by which you may provide us personal information:
By making a reservation or when you purchase services from our website or through our team – by any form of communication e.g. email, letter, facsimile or telephone
By providing the information to us by participating in a marketing campaign or marketing initiative
By visiting and using websites or links that our partners and associated partners are linked to
By visiting and using our website
The type of information normally collected in each of the circumstances is outlined below:
*General - When making a reservation or booking it is necessary to have information in order to identify you, contact you and to process your purchase / service requests. This information usually includes your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and passport number or identity number. It may also include, your preferences regarding the delivery of your service such as type of room, type of bed and associated booking details to ensure the correct allocation and pricing of your request. Your personal information is shared with the third party owner of the hotel (service) where you intend to stay and those of its employees involved in delivering the service to you to the extent necessary for them to do so and to process the transaction.
*Passenger Information - When travel arrangements are made for someone else through ibookholiday.com, we will request personal information and travel preferences about that individual. It is necessary to obtain the consent of other individuals prior to providing ibookholiday.com with their personal information and travel preferences.
*Auto Information - We automatically collect some information about your computer when you visit ibookholiday.com. For example, we will collect your IP address, web browser software (e.g. Mozilla, Firefox or Internet Explorer) and referring website. We also may collect information about your online activity, such as trips viewed and frequent purchases made. The motive in collecting this automatic information is to help customize the website as per user requirements.
*We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features used by third-party advertisers, who serve advertisements across the Internet and may use cookies and other technologies and the information practices of these advertisers are not covered in this privacy policy.
Security of information:
We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption when transmitting your sensitive personal information between your system and our website, we employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your information.
We do not receive and do not store, share, rent or lease sensitive billing information such as your credit card number, cardholder name and expiration date.
Circumstances under which we use your information:
We use information about you generally for the following general purposes. To provide you with the purchase / Service request; to provide you with travel confirmation and updates; to manage your account, including processing bills and providing travel notifications; to communicate with you in general; to respond to your questions and comments; to improve our products, services and website; to notify you about special offers and products or services that may be of interest to you; to otherwise customize your experience with ibookholiday.com; to resolve disputes, collect payments, or troubleshoot problems; to prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities.
We would share information to suppliers, such as hotel, airline, cruise companies, car rental companies, or service providers, who fulfil your purchase / service requests. We do not place limitations on our suppliers' use or disclosure of your other personal information and hence suggest you review the privacy policies of any travel supplier whose products you purchase through ibookholiday.com. Third-party vendors who provide services or functions on our behalf like credit card processing companies. These companies have access to personal information needed to perform their functions in order to process the service request. In response to court orders, or other legal process; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law.
Choice with Respect to Sharing of Information:
It is your discretion and can choose not to provide us with any information, although it may be needed to make and confirm your purchase requests. I Book Holiday has the right to update the privacy policy and will be notified in the website accordingly.
If you have questions about this privacy policy please contact us directly at email address: info@ibookholiday.com
Contact Us :
Rome Evening Tour with Piazza di Spagna and Trevi Fountain in a Small Group
